JULIANA MACEDO



julianamacedo.com



786 493 9208



julianamacedo@knights.ucf.edu

PROFILE

Web and graphic designer with experience building projects using both server-side and client-side languages, producing a wide range of graphic designs, and working on various other digital media projects while creating the best user experience.

EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer

Freelance | August 2020 - Present

- Design unique and interesting graphics while meeting the client's exact needs
- Require little guidance when room for creativity is present and capable of adapting to specific styles

Front End Associate

Sprouts Farmers Market | Oviedo, Florida | June 2021 – Present

- Process customer orders quickly, accurately, and efficiently, while ensuring satisfaction
- Maintain knowledge of weekly advertisement items, product information and location, and events to communicate to customers

Safe Distancing Supervisor

LAZ Parking | Miami Beach, Florida | May 2020 – November 2020

- Supervise safety distancing teams on Miami Beach to ensure compliance of social distancing protocols as directed by the City of Miami Beach
- Implement effective crowd management protocols and promote public safety

Fulfillment Associate | Seasonal

Target | Orlando, Florida | October 2019 – January 2020

- Pick, sort, and pack guest orders to meet service and ship time standards
- Fastest and most efficient fulfillment associate for multiple weeks

Marlins Park Lead Ambassador

SP Plus Corporation | Miami, Florida | May 2019 - September 2019

- Assist with staffing and organizing for all special events at Marlins Park in Miami
- Major events included over 18,000 attendees

Garage Accounting

LAZ Parking | Miami, Florida | Summer 2016, 2017, and 2018

- Work as bookkeeper for second largest parking company in the US with over 15,000 employees
- Responsible for all reconciliation and revenue reporting for parking garage in Miami Beach

EDUCATION

B.A. Digital Media | 3.89 GPA | Anticipated Graduation May 2022 University of Central Florida | Orlando, FL

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, C#
- SQL/MySQL, SASS
- React, React Native
- UX/UI Design
- Adobe Creative Cloud
- Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, Excel
- Visual Design, Branding
- WordPress
- Google Analytics
- Unity
- Databases Management
- Video Production
- Detail-Oriented, Creative Thinker, Organized, Problem Solving,
 Collaborative

LANGUAGES

- English
- Spanish (Beginner)

INTERESTS

- Travel Extensive in USA, Europe, and Asia
- Painting
- · Cooking and Baking
- Yoga